Conservative Party of New York State; Records apap060
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Clippings File, 1962-1987; 8; 12 cubic ft.
  - Transportation, 1965; 1975-1979 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 70)
  - Transportation Bond, 1971 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 71)
  - Transportation Bond, 1973 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 72)
  - Trials, 1978 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 73)
  - "Trib" Pilot Issue, 06/1977 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 74)
  - "Trib", 1977-1978 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 75)
  - "Trib" -- 1st edition, 1978 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 76)
  - Tristate Planning Agency, 1978 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 77)
  - Troy, Matthew, 1971-1978 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 78)
  - Trucks, 1978 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 79)
  - Trump, Donald, 1979 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 80)
  - Turkey, 1974-1978 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 81)
  - Two Party System, 1971 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 82)
  - Udall, Morris, 1975 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 83)
  - UDC (Urban Development Corporation), 1975 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 84)
  - UFT (United Federation of Teachers), 1975 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 85)
  - Uganda, 1972; 1977 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 86)
  - Ulster County, 1970-1971; 1975 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 87)
  - Unemployment, Undated (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 88)
  - Unemployment Funds, 1974; 1977-1978 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 89)
  - Unemployment -- NYS, 1972-1976 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 90)
  - UNICEF, 1965; 1975 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 91)
  - Unions, 1978-1979; 1980; 1983 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 92)
  - United Nations, 1963-1965 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 93)
  - United Nations, 1971-1979 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 94)
  - US Appointments, 1978 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 95)
  - US Attorney General, 1975-1977 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 96)
  - US Attorneys, 1977-1980 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 98)
  - US Budget, 1978 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 99)
  - US Budget, 1979-1980 (Box 11 (8-Clippings File), Folder 100)
  - US Census, 1978-1979 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 1)
  - US Constitutional Amendment, 1972-1973 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 2)
  - US Court of Appeals, 1978 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 3)
  - US Finances, 1970-1980 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 4)
  - US Grand Jury, 1976 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 5)
  - US Information Agency, 1972-1973 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 6)
  - US Labor Party, 1976 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 7)
  - US Laws, 1974 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 8)
  - US Legislation, 1975 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 9)
  - US Legislation, 1976 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 10)
  - US Payroll, 1977 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 11)
  - US Post Office, 1976 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 12)
  - US Primaries, [1979] (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 13)
  - US Prosecutor, Undated (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 14)
  - US Regulations, 1978 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 15)
  - US Senate, 1980; 2 folders (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 16-17)
  - US Senate, 1982 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 18)
  - US Senate Campaign, 1976 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 19)
  - US Senate Filing, 1976 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 20)
  - US Senate Primary, 1976 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 21)
  - US Senate Primary, 1980 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 22)
  - US Senate Race, 1976 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 23)
  - US Supreme Court, 1973-1979; 1987 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 24)
  - US Supreme Court -- Checks & Balances, 1977 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 25)
  - US Supreme Court Decisions, 1971; 1977-1978; 1987 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 26)
  - US Tax, 1979-1980 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 27)
  - US Trade, 1974 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 28)
  - US Trusts, 1979 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 29)
  - Universal Registration, 1977 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 30)
  - Urban, 1977 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 31)
  - Urban Politics, 1978 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 32)
  - Urban Development Corporation, 1971; 1975-1976 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 33)
  - Utilities, 1978 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 34)
  - Value Added Tax, 1979 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 35)
  - Velella, Guy, 1972 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 36)
  - Velez, Ramon S., 1986 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 37)
  - Venereal Disease, 1973 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 38)
  - Vergari, Carl, 1978 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 39)
  - Veterans, 1972-1979 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 40)
  - VFW -- Legislative Program, 1977 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 41)
  - VFW (Queens), 1971; 1976 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 42)
  - Vice President, 1972; 1976; 1978 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 43)
  - Vietnam, 1977-1979 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 44)
  - Vietnam Peace Plan, 1971-1973; 1978 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 45)
  - Viguerie, Richard, 1974-1978 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 46)
  - Violations (Parking), 1976 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 47)
  - Virginia, 1975 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 48)
  - Volunteer Army, 1974 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 49)
  - Voter Legislation, 1978 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 50)
  - Voter Reform, 1977 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 51)
  - Voter Registration, 1971-1973; 1977-1979 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 52)
  - Voting, 1978-1980 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 53)
  - Vouchers, 1973; 1978 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 54)
  - Wachtler, Sol, 1973 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 55)
  - Wage & Price Controls, 1978 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 56)
  - Wagner, Robert, 1964; 1973 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 57)
  - Wagner, Robert F., Jr., 1977 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 58)
  - Wallace, George, 1972-1978 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 59)
  - Walsh, William, 1973-1974 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 60)
  - Ward, Walter, 1977 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 61)
  - Warnke, Paul, 1977 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 62)
  - War -- Mideast, 1973 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 63)
  - War Power, 1973 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 64)
  - Washington County, 1978 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 65)
  - Washington, D.C. Amendment, 1978-1979 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 66)
  - WASP, 1974 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 67)
  - Wayne County, 1976 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 68)
  - Wayne, John, 1976 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 69)
  - Weinstein, Moses, 1977 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 70)
  - Welfare Reform, 1977-1979 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 71)
  - Welfare, 1975-1976 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 72)
  - Wells, William, 1972-1974 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 73)
  - Wemple, Clark, 1977 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 74)
  - West Germany, 1976-1977 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 75)
  - Westchester County, 1968-1980 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 76)
  - Western Union, 1976 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 77)
  - Wharton, Rep, 1962 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 78)
  - Westway Plan, 1977-1978 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 79)
  - Wheat, 1975 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 80)
  - White, F. Clifton, 1973 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 81)
  - Who Represents You, 1981; 1983 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 82)
  - Willowbrook, 1972-1973 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 83)
  - Wilson, Lyle, 1962 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 84)
  - Wilson, Malcolm, 1974 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 85)
  - Wolff, Lester, 1973 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 86)
  - Women, 1974-1979 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 87)
  - Woodside, 1974 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 88)
  - Woodside Herald, 1975 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 89)
  - World Bank, 1977 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 90)
  - Wright, Judge Bruce, 1974; 1979 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 91)
  - Wright, Sam, 1977 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 92)
  - Yankee Stadium, 1973 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 93)
  - YAF, 1971; 1973; 1977 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 94)
  - York College (Jamaica), 1978 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 95)
  - Young, Andrew, 1977-1978 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 96)
  - Young Republicans, 1971 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 97)
  - Youth, 1971 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 98)
  - Youth, 1971-1978 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 99)
  - Youth Crime, 1976-1978 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 100)
  - Youth Criminal Law, 1978 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 101)
  - Youth Rights, 1977 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 102)
  - Zaire, 1977 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 103)
  - Ziegler, Ron, 1975 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 104)
  - Zoning, 1964-1965; 1976 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 105)
  - Zucotti, John, 1975; 1978 (Box 12 (8-Clippings File), Folder 106)
- Queens County Files, 1967; 1970-1980; 1982; 9; 0.5 cubic ft.
  This series contains the records of the Queens County Conservative Party retained with the CPNYS records because of the CPNYS Executive Director's concurrent position as Chairman of the Queens County Conservative Party. It contains materials regarding the Queens County Conservative Party's annual dinners, dinner journals, bulletins, candidates, designating petitions, agendas, rules and regulations, and some correspondence.
  - American Heritage Dinner -- Saluting Mario A. Procaccino, 1974 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 1)
  - American Heritage Dinner -- Saluting Malcolm Wilson, 1975 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 2)
  - American Heritage Dinner -- Saluting Harold Brown, 1976 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 3)
  - American Heritage Dinner -- Saluting Michael J. Maye, 1977 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 4)
  - American Heritage Dinner -- Saluting Stephen J. Crowley, 1978 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 5)
  - American Heritage Dinner -- Saluting Edward V. Regan, 1979 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 6)
  - American Heritage Dinner -- Saluting Lewis Lehrman, 1980 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 7)
  - Annual Dinner Dance, 1969 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 8)
  - Annual Dinner Dance, 1971-1977 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 9)
  - Annual Dinner Dance, 1979 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 10)
  - Annual Dinner Dance, 1980 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 11)
  - Bulletins, 1976 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 12)
  - Bulletins, 1978 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 13)
  - Candidates, 1978 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 14)
  - Candidates, 1985 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 15)
  - Christmas Party, 1979 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 16)
  - Conservative Party Clubs, 1975 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 18)
  - Designating Petitions for Conservative Party -- Queens County Leaders, 1975 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 19)
  - Dinner Journals, 1976; 1980; 1982 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 20)
  - Executive Committee, 1979 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 21)
  - Executive Committee, 1980 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 22)
  - Executive Committee -- Rules & Regulations, 1978 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 23)
  - Executive Committee -- Rules & Regulations, 1979 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 24)
  - Executive Committee -- Rules & Regulations, 1980 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 25)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1980 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 26)
  - Meeting Notices, 1982 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 27)
  - Organizing Meeting -- Proxies, 1980 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 28)
  - Queens County Committee Members, 1974 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 29)
  - Queens County Conservative Party Lists -- Officers, District & Associate District Leaders, 1980 (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 30)
  - Questionnaire by Queens County Conservative Party on Biaggi, Undated; 2 folders (Box 1 (9-Queens County Files), Folder 31-32)
- Buckley Files, 1963; 1965-1980; 1982; 10; 0.5 cubic ft.
  This series contains the records of James L. Buckley and William F. Buckley. The records of James L. Buckley (1968-76) include campaign material, memoranda, newsletters, and news releases, regarding his US Senate campaign and tenure. The records of William F. Buckley include clippings and correspondence (1963, 1965-70, 1974-80, 1982), and campaign materials and position papers for his 1965 New York City Mayoral campaign.
  - James L. Buckley, 1968-1976; 10.1
    - Buckley vs. Valeo -- Motions and Correspondence, 1975 (Box 1 (10-Buckley Files), Folder 1)
    - Campaign Material, 1971; 1976 (Box 1 (10-Buckley Files), Folder 2)
    - Campaign Material -- Speeches and Television Transcripts, 1968; 2 folders (Box 1 (10-Buckley Files), Folder 3-4)
    - Friends of Jim Buckley -- Reelection Material, 1976 (Box 1 (10-Buckley Files), Folder 5)
    - Memoranda to the News Media, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (10-Buckley Files), Folder 6)
    - Newsletters, 1971-1975 (Box 1 (10-Buckley Files), Folder 7)
    - News Releases, 1968; 2 folders (Box 1 (10-Buckley Files), Folder 8-9)
    - News Releases, 1970; 2 folders (Box 1 (10-Buckley Files), Folder 10-11)
    - News Releases, 1971; 1973-1974 (Box 1 (10-Buckley Files), Folder 12)
    - News Releases, 1974-1975 (Box 2 (10-Buckley Files), Folder 13)
    - News Releases, News Releases, 1976 (Box 2 (10-Buckley Files), Folder 14)
  - William F. Buckley, 1963-1982; 10.2
    - Clippings, 1967; 1974-1975; 1978-1980 (Box 2 (10-Buckley Files), Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1963; 1965-1970; 1976; 1979; 1982 (Box 2 (10-Buckley Files), Folder 16)
    - Mayoral Race, 1965 (Box 2 (10-Buckley Files), Folder 17)
    - Position Papers for Mayoral Race, 1965 (Box 2 (10-Buckley Files), Folder 18)
- Audiovisuals, 1993-2004; Undated; 11
  This series includes radio and television interviews, programs, and advertising received from the Conservative Party in October 2006.
  Arranged alphabetically by format.
  - Audiocassette Tapes, 1993-2002; Undated; 11.1
    - "Bankruptcy", New York Conservative Party, 1995 October 23 (Cassette 1)
    - "Blue", NYSCP Campaign Committee Radio, :60, 1996 October 30 (Cassette 2)
    - "Chops", NYSCP, :60, 1997 October 21 (Cassette 3)
    - "Dicker Radio Show", 1999 March 25 (Cassette 4)
    - "Even Better", NYSCP Radio Program, :60, 1998 September 30 (Cassette 5)
    - "Even Better", NYSCP, 1998 October 02 (Cassette 6)
    - "Fred Dicker Show with Mike Long", 1998 January 22 (Cassette 7)
    - "Get It", NYSCP, 1996 January 25 (Cassette 8)
    - "Get It", NYSCP, 1996 February 09 (Cassette 9)
    - "Kemp", New York State Conservative Party, :60, Undated (Cassette 10)
    - "Michael Blomberg", Sean Hannity WABC Am, 60:00, 2001 June 06 (Cassette 11)
    - "Michael Long", WABC AM Radio, 1999 November 30 (Cassette 12)
    - "Michael Long with Pat Cunnengham", Radio Show, 1996 June 11 (Cassette 13)
    - "MRL", with NBC CH.4, 1997 November 11 (Cassette 14)
    - "MRL on Fred Dicker Radio Program", 1998 August 14 (Cassette 15)
    - "On the Line", WNYC Michael Long, 1999 December 02 (Cassette 16)
    - "Onondaga City Meeting", 1993 January 12 (Cassette 17)
    - "Pataki Express", Nassau County Conservative Party, 1998 October 09 (Cassette 18)
    - "Silver, Follow, Tax Cut", Change NY, :60, 1995 March 23 (Cassette 19)
    - "Teeth 3", NYSCP Radio Program, :60, 1997 June 16 (Cassette 20)
    - "Too Far", NYSCP, 1996 June 03 (Cassette 21)
    - "Unborn Victim", NYSCP Radio Program, :60, 2002 March 26 (Cassette 22)
    - "Vote", NYSCP Campaign Committee Radio, :60, 1996 October 30 (Cassette 23)
    - "Wisdom", NYSCP Radio Program, :60, 1997 June 20 (Cassette 24)
  - Compact Disks, 2000; Undated; 11.2
    - "NYSCP Bundle", AVI MOV ASF, Undated (Cd 1)
    - "NYSCP Snapshot", AVI MOV MPEG, 2000 July 13 (Cd 2)
    - "Operation TV Spot", Warfield And Company AVI MOV, Undated (Cd 3)
  - Videocassette Tapes, VHS, 1993-2004; Undated; 11.3
    - "Abortion Interview with Michael Long", NY1 TV News, 2:41, 1999 August 18 (Video-tape 1)
    - "Alan Roth", New York Market RNN Big Story, :19, 2000 October 03 (Video-tape 2)
    - "Assemblyman John J. Faso Speech", Republican State Convention, 1994 May 25 (Video-tape 3)
    - "Bogsted For The Conservative Party", The EGC Group, :30, Undated (Video-tape 4)
    - "Boycott the Boss", unknown, Undated (Video-tape 5)
    - "Bush Conservative Lunch", 2000 July 14 (Video-tape 6)
    - "Bush For President", Conservative Party of New York, 5:28, 2000 May 12 (Video-tape 7)
    - "Bush for President", Conservative Party of New York, 5:28, 2000 May 12 (Video-tape 8)
    - "Bush Headlines New York State Conservative Party Luncheon", New York Market WABC News, :19, 2000 July 14 (Video-tape 9)
    - "Charter Revision Protest", NY1 News, 1:21, 1999 August 05 (Video-tape 10)
    - "Compassion", CPTV New York Conservative Party, :30, 1996 February 09 (Video-tape 11)
    - "Compassion", CPTV New York Conservative Party, :30, 1996 February 13 (Video-tape 12)
    - "Conservative Party Dinner", NY1 News, 1:39, 1999 May 20 (Video-tape 13)
    - "Crossfire", CNN National Cable Market, 4:50, 2000 February 07 (Video-tape 14)
    - "Face Off", Episode 1016, 2003 October 27 (Video-tape 15)
    - "Face Off", Episode 1036, 2004 April 26 (Video-tape 16)
    - "Face Off", Unknown Episode, Undated (Video-tape 17)
    - "Face Off", Unknown Episode (October 19), Undated (Video-tape 18)
    - "Face Off", Unknown Episode, 1999 September 09 (Video-tape 19)
    - "Face Off", Unknown Episode (June 28), Undated (Video-tape 20)
    - "Face Off", Unknown Episode, 2000 April 13 (Video-tape 21)
    - "FBI", Betty Hoffman for Senate, :30, 1995 February 24 (Video-tape 22)
    - "Finally, State", Marlin for Mayor, 1:00:00, 1993 October 16 (Video-tape 23)
    - "Finest & Bravest", New York State Conservative Party, :10, 2001 June 29 (Video-tape 24)
    - "Gray for Mayor", Sit down, :30, 2001 October 17 (Video-tape 25)
    - "Gray For Mayor", Sit Down, :30, 2001 October 17 (Video-tape 26)
    - "Hardball CNBC, Brit Hume FNC, WNBC", Michael Long TV News, 1999 November 30 (Video-tape 27)
    - "Hillary Clinton Complains About Mailers From Conservatives", National Market, 9:25, 2000 July 17 (Video-tape 28)
    - "Hoops", NY State Conservative Party, :30, 1997 October 17 (Video-tape 29)
    - "Inside City Hall", NY-1-TV Interview with Mike Long, 21:56, 1998 January 23 (Video-tape 30)
    - "Inside City Hall", NY1 Michael Long, 1999 December 03 (Video-tape 31)
    - "Inside City Hall", NY1 News, 1999 December 30 (Video-tape 32)
    - "Inside City Hall", NY1 New York Market, 5:30, 2001 March 06 (Video-tape 33)
    - "Interview with Mike Long Discusses Hillary Clinton" FNC TV Special Report with Brit Home, 3:54, 1999 June 04 (Video-tape 34)
    - "Interview with Michael Long", NY1 TV News, 1999 August 07 (Video-tape 35)
    - "Interview with Mike Long", New York Market WABC Eyewitness News Upclose, 22:07, 2001 June 10 (Video-tape 36)
    - "Key Issues Facing NY Voters", unknown, Undated (Video-tape 37)
    - "Larry King Live", CNN national Cable Market, 9:13, 2000 February 07 (Video-tape 38)
    - "Lazio/G.W. Busch", NYSCP Footage, 55:00, Undated (Video-tape 39)
    - "Lazio's Concession Speech", New York Market WNYW NY1 News, 2000 November 07 (Video-tape 40)
    - "Lulac Speech", George W. Bush, Undated (Video-tape 41)
    - "Michael Long", WNBC News, 3:19, 1999 August 06 (Video-tape 42)
    - "Michael Long", NY1 News, 3:48, 1999 August 07 (Video-tape 43)
    - "Michael Long", CBS TV Sunday Edition, 22:00, 1999 August 22 (Video-tape 44)
    - "Michael Long", WNBC TV News Forum, 1999 December 05 (Video-tape 45)
    - "Michael Long", WCBS Sunday Edition News, 11:00, 2000 January 09 (Video-tape 46)
    - "Michael Long & Pat Buchanan" NY1 News, 4:37, 2000 January 08 (Video-tape 47)
    - "Michael Long", WNBC New York Market, 3:17, 2000 May 01 (Video-tape 48)
    - "Michael Long", NY1 Inside City Hall, 2:43, 2000 May 01 (Video-tape 49)
    - "Michael Long", FNC Fox News Now, 5:30, 2000 May 01 (Video-tape 50)
    - "Michael Long", FNC Special Report with Brit Hume, 2:36, 2000 May 01 (Video-tape 51)
    - "Michael Long", MNBC Special Edition, 5:50, 2000 May 19 (Video-tape 52)
    - "Mike Long", National Cable Market MNBC The News with Brian Williams, 6:40, 2000 July 07 (Video-tape 53)
    - "Mike Long", National Cable Market FNC Special Report with Brit Hume, 3:02, 2000 July 07 (Video-tape 54)
    - "Mike Long", New York Market WLIW Face Off, 30:00, 2000 October 20 (Video-tape 55)
    - "Mike Long" New York Market WCBS, 2:55, 2000 April 28 (Video-tape 56)
    - "Mike Long May Not Back Guiliani", WCBS New York Market, :54, 2000 March 21 (Video-tape 57)
    - "Mrs. Don Sutton Premature Baby", 1997 February (Video-tape 58)
    - "Nassau County Tax", WABC WNBC WCBS News, 1999 August 10 (Video-tape 59)
    - "Nassau County Tax", WABC News, 2:31, 1999 August 11 (Video-tape 60)
    - "National Cable Market", Michael Long, The O'Reilly Factor, 5:13, 2000 April 03 (Video-tape 61)
    - "National Cable Market", Governor George Pataki, PBS NewsHour with Jim Lehrer, 9:30, 2000 April 12 (Video-tape 62)
    - "National Cable Market", Michael Long, FNC Fox News Now, 1:50, 2000 May 18 (Video-tape 63)
    - "National Cable Market", FNC Special Report with Brit Hume, New York Conservative Party, 3:25, 2000 June 01 (Video-tape 64)
    - "National Cable Market", Special with Brit Hume Michael Long, 2:15, 2000 September 18 (Video-tape 65)
    - "National Cable Market", Michael Long, FNC Special Report with Brit Hume, 2:30, 2000 September 28 (Video-tape 66)
    - "National Right to Life Partial Birth Abortion Spots", 3:23, 1998 August 21 (Video-tape 67)
    - "New York Conservative Party Annual Fund Raising", Undated (Video-tape 68)
    - "New York Conservative Party Luncheon", New York Market, WCBS News WABC News WNBC News, 2000 July 14 (Video-tape 69)
    - "New York Market", Michael Long, Rudy Giuliani, WCBS News 2 at 6, 2:52, 2000 April 10 (Video-tape 70)
    - "New York Market", Michael Long, New York Conservative Party, WB11 Ten O'clock News, 2:40, 2000 May 22 (Video-tape 71)
    - "New York Market", Michael Long, WPIX Ten O'clock News, 4:50, 2000 May 22 (Video-tape 72)
    - "New York Market", Michael Long, NY1 Close Up, 11:50, 2000 May 23 (Video-tape 73)
    - "New York Market", Inside City Hall Michael Long, 2:15, 2000 September 18 (Video-tape 74)
    - "New York Market", WNYW The Ten O'clock News, 2:30, 2000 September 28 (Video-tape 75)
    - "New York Market", Michael Long would give Party Seat to Giuliani, WCBS First News at 4, 5:00, 2001 September 24 (Video-tape 76)
    - "New York Market", Michael Long would give Party Seat to Giuliani, WNBC NBC News Channel 4, 3:00, 2001 September 24 (Video-tape 77)
    - "New York Market", Michael Long would give Party Seat to Giuliani NY1, Inside City Hall, 3:00, 2001 September 24 (Video-tape 78)
    - "New York Market", WNBC Eyewitness News at 6, 2:57, 2001 October 03 (Video-tape 79)
    - "New York Senate Race", WNYW Fox FNC Special Report with Brit Hume, 2000 February 08 (Video-tape 80)
    - "Not Worth Dying For" American Conservative Union, 1994 August 03 (Video-tape 81)
    - "New York Conservative Party Annual Fund Raising Dinner", FNC Fox News Now, :50, 2000 May 18 (Video-tape 82)
    - "New York Conservative Party Annual Fund Raising Dinner", FNC Special Report with Brit Hume, 8:20, 2000 May 19 (Video-tape 83)
    - "New York State Dinner", Conservative Party, 1995 (Video-tape 84)